(Previously)
XY Island Battle.
This game has found its true king.
Choose your crush.
I choose...
I choose
I choose you.
(Episode 3: Getting Closer
Frame by Frame)
Then Young,
my turn, right?
Yes.
Then I...
I'll choose,
I'll choose Joel, I guess.
Then I'll go with
then we two
I'll go with that one, right.
Back to the room.
Back to the warm harbor.
What are you thinking?
Isn't this water a bit deep?
(Deep???)
It's actually warm.
He didn't spray sunscreen either.
After we take off our clothes, we'll
spray some on each other.
Sure.
Let me spray some
sunscreen on you, come on.
(Feel the Glow)
Spray the arms first.
I'll stay away from their watermelon.
(Photographer Capturing...)
We're good over here.
OK.
Rub it in, your neck.
Come on.
This really...
Do you want to try?
You sit on it and try first.
And then it'll be like this.
(It seems like it's going to tip)
Let me help you hold it.
Come on, be brave.
Sit down slowly.
Sit.
Come on.
Sit a bit more in the middle.
If you sit on either
end, it'll definitely tip.
Already soaked.
I'm crawling around here now.
OK, it's fine now.
Get up, I can't even hold it down.
I can't hold it down.
Coming up.
OK.
Bro.
I think the safest way
is like this.
To be honest,
can you keep your balance?
Of course not.
Then try again.
Let me pour the water out and try.
Do you need help?
No need.
Just help me pour the water out.
Then you sit in the middle.
I'll help hold it for you.
One more time.
Steady now.
OK.
This thing is hard.
(Okay, okay, I give up)
It's fine. Damn.
Let's restart.
Help!
Steady.
OK.
Just like that.
Need to put it over your head.
I can totally do.
I can totally do this.
It's because I'm holding it up.
We two have to prevent
any accidents at all times.
What are you doing?
Come.
Sit in the middle.
A different pose.
Change the pose.
I have a pose.
So you sit here,
and then you lean closer.
In the frame, it looks pretty good.
Let me see.
How did they design theirs?
(Joining the crowd)
Wait, hold on.
Wait, I suddenly realized
we're swimming,
how can our hair be dry?
In order for us to get first place,
I'll give it my all.
Oh no, my makeup is all ruined.
It doesn't matter.
He is a person with a plan.
He knows what he looks like,
what looks good,
and what looks expressive.
So he'll arrange
and come up with
some very interesting things.
Do you want to pump up?
Trust me, if you pump up,
you'll look really good.
Trust me.
Let me pump my muscles.
OK.
I'm pumped.
You lie on top, I'll lie
I'll lie down.
Never mind, I'll lie down.
You can come behind me.
There's also a concave part here.
Do you have double pectorals?
I have double pectorals.
Then look at my chest shape.
You also have double.
But I feel you,
but your chest has great natural potential.
Really?
Your chest is really much better than mine.
It's just my lower chest
I can't develop.
What other poses do you have?
Think some more.
I'll do it.
Or you lie down,
and then I push up like this.
The main idea is that I'm talking,
and he's more...
just going along with me to complete it.
I think Joel is the kind of person,
umm, if you have
something you want to do,
he's the type who will do it with you.
I'm getting shy from you looking.
No, it's the light that's too strong,
I can't open my eyes.
Did you take the shot, bro?
They've been shooting the whole time.
The two of us should lie down together
on this boat and then shoot.
Come on, you sit on top.
Here I come again.
(Piece of cake)
I'm controlling it.
Come.
My hair is okay, right?
Or too messy?
I'm a bit blocked.
You need to help me,
pull me back a bit.
It's fine, I'll just hold
it like this for you.
I found a brilliant idea.
Because I often take photos,
so I definitely have
some of my own ideas.
The prop we chose was
the transparent boat.
My idea was
to have a height-difference
eye contact with him.
And that would give a bit of
a certain feeling.
They don't need us watching.
Yeah, we can't even watch at all.
Then let's not watch then.
Just keep the mystery.
Have you guys already planned it out?
We're just waiting for the
promotional shoot to finish,
then we can shoot.
Yeah, our idea is amazing.
Us too.
(You can't fool me!)
OK, not telling you.
Let me see what you guys are shooting.
Hello.
Bath towels?
No, what kind of photo are you taking?
Do you have a reference picture?
Hello.
Come on, look at the camera.
No, our video.
("Totally" Casual)
It doesn't have anything fixed.
Let me look for some.
I need to find some references.
Your bath towels
definitely have reference pictures.
Want to hold you into my body.
Quick, let me see.
No, I'm thinking.
What?
Searched from these keywords.
How did you get?
What do you mean?
What did you search exactly?
He's filming us.
No, it's fine.
I'm currently looking for
how to shoot our video.
I'm thinking about the video now.
Your bracelet is so cute.
I'll give you one.
Then I won't be polite.
How can you exchange gifts in front of me?
YES.
What are you doing?
The fourth person has joined.
Talking about this.
Isn't that his?
How did it become
a world of four people?
We're the ones going to see
the meteor shower together.
What's that?
(Tired... )
No.
Cheer up!
I need to save my energy
and wait for the shoot.
OK, sure.
I heard your story
is amazing.
Right?
Yeah.
We're definitely getting first place.
Really?
Then he'll deliberately not vote for us.
Is that your CCD camera?
Yes.
Seems a bit close.
I'll move farther.
Caused by half a watermelon.
What do you think?
This is okay.
This can work.
This one is theirs.
Yeah, this works.
I think when we're together,
we get along very comfortably.
And very relaxed.
Can you hold it now?
Ready, everyone?
Can we switch now?
I think we can switch.
Careful.
And I have one more.
This clip should be enough.
And the video, I don't know if they
have edited it out yet.
It's our turn.
We're going to change.
We think it's OK.
Let me find my sunscreen.
I think this look is fine.
Even if the hair is a bit wet, it's fine.
Sure, the sun is quite strong today.
Let's spray some sunscreen.
Sure, let me spray for you.
Sit down.
Where do you want to spray?
Just spray the hands.
Arms.
Do you want me to spray you?
Sure, help me spray.
Help me spray my neck.
OK.
You can rub it in.
Almost.
Then let's go.
Take a sunscreen down.
Let's go.
They haven't finished yet.
Let's discuss it a bit more.
How about this?
You stand here.
Would it be too tall?
I think standing is fine for me.
You sit here.
Because you're taller than me,
right?
Probably.
So cold.
Let me swim a bit.
Coming.
Come on.
Young's eyes are too affectionate.
I really couldn't handle it at that moment.
Can we end now? Any more?
No more, bro.
I've given it my all.
I can't think of any more poses.
I want to borrow
their bathroom, is that okay?
I'm soaked all over.
You have put in a lot of effort.
Soaked all over.
Hurry, don't catch a cold.
Because there's air conditioning inside.
Which setting do you think would be better?
Then I think.
Is your left side or right side better?
Right side.
Right side, right?
Right side means this side.
Then you are.
Your right side means
you probably need to be here.
Do we need to be at a corner?
Yes.
I'll be in front first.
I'm over there, right?
Wait, fix your hair first.
Wet it first?
Yes, okay?
Or should I help you?
Wet it.
Right here.
No, it's the bangs.
Need to comb them down.
Should the back be wet?
The back doesn't need to be seen.
Because we're just shooting this.
Just look at me from this side.
Then just look at me.
Can I see?
I want to see, I don't know,
because I don't know
how it turned out.
Or you can look down now.
When you're on my side, just look down.
Let's do another set
with swapped positions.
And this time you're in front,
and I'm behind.
Should I look down?
You can look down or look up, either works.
Because that time,
actually the time was very short.
And we had to shoot video,
so I was actually very anxious.
So maybe I tended to
impose my own ideas forcefully.
Maybe that's not very good.
I don't know if it made him uncomfortable.
And I also hope
that he has his own ideas,
or that he might
have some new presentation [idea]
and then maybe tell me,
but whatever I say,
he says OK.
Maybe he just trusts me more.
I have another idea.
Let's both take off our
shirts and lie down here.
And then like this.
Just like this.
You look at the duck,
and I look at you.
He kept guiding me on how
to pose,
or eye contact.
I think we worked together pretty well.
Look at that.
When you adjust the duck,
I might turn around,
and then you just happen to meet
our eyes meeting.
And then you
might slowly, slowly cut it.
Or you can also look at me.
OK.
Almost done.
OK, let's go.
Wrap this over.
They seem to have finished shooting.
I'll go check on the balcony.
What?
Are you done?
Done.
OK.
We're about ready.
What are you doing?
Packing up clothes.
Did you spray sunscreen before going out?
Not yet.
I brought it.
Let me spray for you.
OK, wait.
I'll spray for you later too.
OK, no problem.
Twist it.
Neck.
Help me spray my neck.
OK, rub it in.
OK.
Help me.
OK, thanks.
SORRY.
It's fine.
Apply thickly.
OK.
Alright.
You do this,
apply some more.
OK.
Let's go.
Hurry down and shoot.
Wait, don't we need to get wet first?
We need to get wet first, right?
Or do we just jump in?
I think we should just jump in.
Really?
That works too.
OK, then let's first
leave it there.
I think put it over there.
Put it
on your side.
On my side.
It's a bit cold up here.
Hands can only be placed on top.
There's a height difference.
I'll sit a bit higher.
My hands can only rest on the outside.
Don't let him see.
OK.
Just two people leaning
shoulder to shoulder,
and
our faces actually very close,
looking into each other's eyes.
I think this is actually
very intimate.
It's just that for the two of us, regarding
decision-making and judgment,
plus choices,
these are aligned.
And our aesthetics are also in sync.
I feel like we're cooperating
to complete a task together.
Move forward a bit.
Good brother.
Like holding a pipa half-hiding the face.
I should probably break off a big piece.
Put the irregular piece in your mouth.
Like this.
Yes.
Come on.
Why don't you take a look?
Then I'm from behind,
From this spot. It
should be from this spot.
And then I do this.
Straight shot.
I think a bit more to the back.
A bit back.
I'll turn around.
I'll go this way.
Then I'll be like this.
Like this.
I'm going to break character.
The task,
I treated it as
a real assignment given to me.
So I really wanted to seriously
complete this task.
I just wanted to do this perfectly.
Come on, look here.
Are you taking a selfie?
Yes.
Take a look.
Not bad.
Quick, look at them shooting.
They're feeding each other
watermelon mouth to mouth.
Yeah, they should be like that.
Even more passionate than us.
They're like that,
feeding mouth to mouth.
Because today when the other two groups
were shooting,
I also watched from above.
I think Tyler and CH's
first group's expressiveness is good.
Great, awesome.
OK.
Done.
Great work.
Finally done.
We worked hard.
I'll put the watermelon here.
Come on.
Pool party!
Join our pool party.
Come in quickly.
Come on, let's have a water fight then.
Come play, everyone play together.
Best CP photo selection.
Come on. Let's go.
Finally we can see the final photos.
Then our group will sit together.
(Best CP photo selection)
Come on.
The vote is coming, right?
That means it's time to vote.
For some reason, I feel a bit embarrassed.
How to play, the remote?
The remote is with me.
Let me see how to adjust.
About to play.
So excited.
Very nice.
Actually it's okay.
Actually not bad.
I think it's very nice.
But I think his movement
shots will be better.
Tyler's group.
I think their group shot really well.
Really shot well.
I think there must be
a deep,
very deep bond between them.
The first group's work
is full of tension overall.
It amazed me.
You can tell they all
put in a lot of effort.
Hurry up and skip!
Next group, teacher.
These two people.
OK, next one.
Don't look. I don't want to.
What should I do...
So Japanese-style.
Pretty.
I don't know.
Totally different from what I imagined.
Maybe my reference picture was like this.
Also completely different
from what we imagined.
We'll see ours later.
Don't be nervous.
The results aren't out yet.
(Super Confident!)
Let's not be nervous.
OK, next one.
Don't look anymore.
Don't want to see anymore.
Seeing their final results,
it really good.
I wonder if our results
will be this good.
After seeing his work,
I'm suddenly not so confident.
I think the first one is very good.
Yeah, the first one is very nice.
Very good because...
Let's look at the next group.
Look, no.
No.
Look at you two.
You two don't look like you're in
that pool,
you two look like you're in a bathhouse.
How to say this?
This is really good.
Our group is quite
quite satisfied.
I think we might
get the most votes.
Do you want to watch it again?
Does everyone need to watch again?
I don't think everyone
really needs to see it again.
OK, come on.
Now let's vote.
Come on.
If two people aren't sure,
then why not one vote each,
that way it's faster.
Then raise your hands.
Each person only has one vote.
At that time we probably
shouldn't vote, just us.
No, you think.
Do you want to see?
We don't want to see this.
No.
If you want to see, we'll
just tell you the result.
Do you want to see who voted?
We're not watching.
OK, sure.
Raise your hands for the first group.
Three.
Two.
One.
OK.
OK, announcing the results.
Two votes.
Two votes, first group gets two votes.
OK.
OK, let's vote.
Vote for the second group,
raise your hands.
Three.
Two.
One.
Announce.
I also vote for them.
OK, bro, got it.
Three votes.
Second group gets three votes.
Then from the third group.
Three.
Two.
One.
OK.
One vote.
Congratulations.
Congratulations to our second group.
Thanks for the support.
Well-deserved.
I'm very happy that everyone
likes our photos.
And
actually it was mostly.
Elio who came up with the ideas.
And he probably has more experience.
It's great.
No, what about the first group?
Winning, you are first place.
First place means for the next game,
for the next game you
you can go first to complete it.
Yes.
OK, thanks.
Priority choice.
We can eat now, right?
Then let's go eat.
Time to eat.
There's this.
Actually I want to see
more of this bowl of rice.
I have a good appetite now.
I'll start eating.
So delicious.
How long has it been since you
lived with so many people
together?
No need, I know.
This red chili is too spicy.
So you all
have acting experience?
Because he studied acting.
I have.
He's also an actor.
We all have.
But I didn't study acting.
No, I haven't learned.
What did you do before?
I've done all kinds of jobs.
I've done cooking work, and...
I've worked in the back kitchen,
washed dishes, passed dishes,
then did sales,
and also did modeling.
So I've done all kinds of jobs.
I like trying different things.
You want to experience different lives.
Yes, I like that.
I'm quite curious about this world.
If possible,
without those certificates
or career restrictions,
I'd even want to experience
every profession in this world.
When I heard Young say
about his experiences,
at his age,
to be able to do so many jobs,
I think it's amazing.
Because I've never had such experiences.
So I said wow,
you're amazing.
I think he is
a very thoughtful boy.
He keeps trying.
I think that's pretty cool.
So I look at him
with a very appreciative
perspective.
When I just graduated,
I worked in a hospital for a while.
A hospital?
What was your major?
Biomedical engineering.
Really?
Yes, and at that time I was
working in the operating room.
The operating room?
Yes.
Just assisting doctors with things like
hemostats,
and helping wipe sweat,
or perhaps
no,
controlling the instruments and stuff.
The monitoring equipment and such.
Then the pressure you guys have.
It feels to me even greater than,
I think it's even more
stressful than being a doctor.
So I didn't really like it.
I didn't really like it.
Then later I went
and opened a pet shop.
So you've never had
acting experience?
Not too much.
Because I really like having pets,
I've liked these things since childhood.
One day, can you give my dog
a haircut?
Sure.
You want a freebie, bro?
Just kidding.
Just joking.
I also want a bottle of water, thanks.
OK, who else wants?
Does anyone want water?
I want one too.
Me too.
I also want one, thanks.
OK.
One more bottle missing.
OK, just enough.
Thanks.
His major is also a bit
bio-
He's biomedical, I'm pharmacy.
So you've also been a doctor?
No, that's not a doctor.
Because we're not clinical medicine,
we can only do things like
pharmacy or
pharmacist.
Pharmacist and stuff, we
actually still have differences.
So you have many, many skills.
But each one,
I think none of them are particularly
at the peak of perfection.
Right, I just want
to be an experiencer.
After you experience a hundred kinds,
you'll feel there's always one
that you want to do really well.
I think in this process,
you get to know yourself better.
Really, more skills don't weigh you down.
Why did you suddenly want to come?
For what reason did we
come here?
I need to think about this one.
No need.
I was just casually asking.
For me,
it's about experiencing a different life.
Then I think.
I
am curious about the acting profession.
Quite curious.
Yes, that's it.
Us too, just curious.
I think we two are a bit alike.
So you are
first time with so many cameras?
Yes.
How do you feel?
Not bad.
Actually, I want to play a domineering CEO.
Anyway, the skits and online
dramas that have emerged later.
I didn’t even have a chance
to play the role of the boss.
One day I want to play the role of boss.
Mainly because he's handsome, rich,
young, and cold.
Who wouldn't,
which man wouldn't want to experience that?
Do you? What role do you want to play?
I want
to play myself.
I think before
having enough life experience,
I think being able to play yourself well
is already a very difficult thing.
So if you had
a script given to you,
what kind of role would you want to play?
A role close to myself,
a role I can handle.
Modern drama or period drama?
Modern drama.
What is your positioning of yourself?
What kind of role?
What do you think your positioning
is?
Feels like there are countless microphones
in front of him.
I don't know either.
I just play whatever,
the eldest son.
Child abuse? (misheard)
Eldest son.
Wait, you just said
you need enough experience to play these,
and now you
eldest son?
He just has
the eldest son in the family
no.
What I mean is
play a child,
play a son,
play a son, play a student,
play a young person just entering society.
Things I've experienced.
Pretty much what I guessed.
We think you're very suitable
for campus dramas,
or the kind of
maybe from a well-off family,
whose family runs a company,
that kind of
also a CEO type.
Yeah, that kind of kid.
No, it's not quite the same as a CEO.
A spoiled rich kid.
Yes.
That is
maybe someone who's been set up.
Starting a business from nothing,
entrepreneurship,
first-generation entrepreneur.
Do you have a role you want to play?
I think what I said is similar to him.
I want to play [something]
comfortable, suitable,
close to myself.
Closer.
Yes, because
actually I've studied
a little bit of acting.
And that teacher also said
that actually actors just need to
play themselves well.
Play yourself well,
I think that's great.
Just stick to one type of role,
and you'll get many roles.
Yeah, I think the same.
I plan to play CEO for life.
Just kidding.
Actually I can do anything.
You're so cute, oh my.
Actually I
"I want to play CEO for life."
Later when we have
we'll let him have all the CEO roles.
OK.
We'll give them all to him.
Wait, wasn't I the last one to arrive?
And do you all
each have a crush gift?
Yes.
We prepared them ourselves,
little items representing ourselves.
Your gift is?
The gift is a skateboard.
After eating, how about we
put our chosen gifts over there,
under our photo wall.
Now tell us everyone's gifts,
and then you guess
which one belongs to whom, okay?
OK.
What are our gifts?
A bracelet.
The kind used for pets,
like a hanging collar.
The second is that CCD camera.
The third is earphones.
The fourth is a lollipop.
The fifth is the pallet.
Is the pallet Elio's?
That's too easy.
There are four.
Because here only he can draw,
and when he came he drew that for us.
Who owns the neck strap?
Or you can guess the others first.
Lollipop.
Who owns the lollipop?
You can guess.
Just guess.
Tyler's, I guess.
Correct.
Yes.
How come
you knew it was his?
Because "tang" (sugar).
Very clever.
So I thought it was Tyler.
So after all that,
I actually should have brought a
peach. [Homophone for his last name]
Next is the CCD.
CCD.
CCD, the one I just said.
The pet necklace isn't his.
Oh no, this elimination method.
Now we're eliminating.
Why?
This is to make it harder for you.
Otherwise your elimination won't work.
Actually the two straps,
we're left to choose between those two.
But.
But besides CCD, what else?
Earphones.
It's a bit hard.
These three feel...
It's too everyday,
too ordinary, no connection.
Guess.
It's okay if you're wrong.
I think the earphones are his.
Because I think you
like listening to music.
I think he likes music.
Total failure.
None correct.
That's the three of us,
you got none right.
Only these two you got right.
OK, announce it.
Reveal the answers.
I've actually already eliminated,
now I know
the earphones are yours,
and you're the CCD,
and you're the cat strap.
So I want to know the reasons.
The reason is because I
have a Ragdoll cat,
and have spent a long time with it.
I feel it has already
become like my child.
How long have you had it?
Over a year,
almost two years.
So why is yours the CCD?
I brought the CCD because I think
I might be more introverted,
and
like to take photos.
So I use
photos
to record.
I use photos to record everyone
Express emotions through photos,
I think you could say that.
Why are you the earphones?
Because normally my energy
is quite full most of the time,
but many times I will
while chatting with you,
in the middle of talking,
I suddenly stop talking,
my whole self suddenly feels
like I've shut myself off.
So I really need
something that can help me
isolate myself from the
outside or from things.
I heard a saying before
that the distinction between I and E people
isn't actually about
introversion and extroversion,
but refers to your choices
in an unfamiliar environment.
For example,
they say E people
in an unfamiliar environment
feel very relaxed,
and they feel
that it doesn't matter what they do.
But I people are not,
I people feel
"Should I be doing something?"
"Should I initiate a topic to
ease my own awkwardness?"
So
that's why people think
that I people can seem
very E among E people.
He starts from the overall perspective,
he might be more concerned with
how you might feel,
rather than what I should do.
That's it.
Yes.
But I am
someone who must socialize.
You're an E person.
Yes, he's EN.
I and E means
I gets energy from being alone,
E gets energy from socializing.
I must socialize,
I can't be alone.
Then I don't seem to be,
because I'm an E person,
but I don't necessarily have to
get energy from socializing.
I actually spend more time alone.
It's not that he
must socialize,
but socializing is a bigger
way to gain energy.
For example, being alone gives 20%,
but socializing gives me 80%.
That's how it is.
I'm the type
that socializing is okay,
but if no one talks, it's quiet,
just doing my own thing.
So that's why
I always find
many things to do for myself.
That's the reason.
So what E are you?
I'm ENFJ.
Protagonist, big protagonist.
Big protagonist.
All of us here are NF.
I'm SP.
Then we're all NF.
You are
actually more rational in most cases,
in most situations.
Yes, because I used to be.
INFP.
The little butterfly.
And I had
anxiety,
at night,
like if I overthink,
anxious to the point that
I can't sleep all night.
So I forcibly
changed my personality,
and went from N to.
S.
And now
he takes things as they come.
That's it.
I might just think about it,
and then walk away.
Yes.
Now I just avoid,
but it's not really avoidance.
Actually I think it's pretty good.
Sometimes this insensitivity
is quite important.
I feel around us
I often see these personalities.
I think that's right.
Big sword, the campaigner.
The mediator and the advocate.
These people cover 80%.
Green personality gathering.
Yes.
I think it might be related to
what we studied.
There won't be any tasks tonight, right?
Probably not.
Today should be...
He won't come again at
7 AM tomorrow, will he?
Then I'll go help everyone
get the crush items.
Sure.
Actually,
I really don't know.
Everyone's back.
Got them.
Then let's go over there directly.
Let's go directly.
Let's go.
Place them
under the photo wall.
Photos.
Just place them on this shelf.
That works too.
Because it symbolizes
that we're all together.
OK.
Very good.
One, two.
You can record it.
OK, fine.
Polaroid.
Probably not.
Yes.
OK.
There should be.
Yes.
Let's stick it up.
Done.
The doorbell rang.
Then I'll go.
Another task.
No way, I need to sleep.
It's raining outside.
Still the voting segment.
Still voting.
Today's XY crush vote is open.
Within 15 minutes, write down
the name of the person you
feel most drawn to and why.
Complete today's crush vote.
After 30 minutes,
all contestants gather in the living room.
Come on.
Let's go.
Same old segment.
Come on, take one each.
Yesterday you saw,
actually you can imitate
someone else's handwriting.
You two aren't
imitating our handwriting
secretly, are you?
I think we two get along quite well.
I think we're quite complementary
in terms of personality.
CH, I guess.
I don't know.
Can't say.
Let me add my little pillow.
People's feelings can change
at any time.
Vote for... I still vote for Joel.
That's without question.
Because I think
the time spent with Joel
is the longest.
I voted for Waner.
Today was quite happy,
working with him was quite enjoyable.
We also got first place.
Just based on looks,
in my opinion,
I think Waner is the best-looking.
The voting results are here.
OK.
I'll announce the results.
Is everyone nervous?
What do you think?
Hurry up.
OK.
Today's voting results.
First is Waner.
Two votes.
Second is CH.
Tyler,
zero votes.
Joel,
one vote.
Young,
Elio,
zero votes.
A bit
a bit
a bit disappointed.
Thoughts?
Thoughts are very sad.
The one with the fewest votes,
please go to the XY coordinate zone.
You may only choose
one person's box to open,
or choose not to open any.
Check their voting result.
So it's just the two of us going.
Which of you two first?
Let's go.
Then I'll go first.
Go ahead.
Let me go take a look.
I feel very surprised.
Yes.
Just
because I felt they
had quite high votes yesterday.
Come on.
Is it my turn to look?
Right?
Just look at CH's.
I feel very sad.
This afternoon mainly
was shooting those photos.
And
actually most of the
time spent together was one-on-one.
He wrote a few words for someone else:
"very pleasing to the eye,"
"comfortable to be with."
So the meaning is basically
maybe
being with me
is not comfortable.
So it hurts.
Then
reduce the time together.
Definitely need to cut losses in time.
I'm not an idiot.
OK.
I feel even more guilty.
I know that Tyler
got zero votes.
Actually I was thinking,
just
I was a bit shaken.
Because today I've been paired with him
as CP.
Including when we shot
the swimsuit photos today,
I could actually feel that
we both are the type with strong execution,
and both have strong ideas,
and we click instantly.
And actually today I was also thinking
whether tonight I
should try voting for Tyler once.
The thing I was hesitant about
is because I think.
Tyler is a person whose personality is also
straightforward and fiery.
So my personality,
I'm actually not that fiery.
I think this is a very
important point.
OK.
They will start reasoning again at night.
Start reasoning.
Let’s see who I will do
the task with tomorrow.
It’s all unknown now.
I can accept that
tomorrow is still zero votes.
Anyway, it’s twice.
I‘m surprised that he has zero votes today.
I don’t think this should be the result.
If I have one more vote, I
will definitely vote for him.
Young, in my opinion,
he is a very real and gentle person.
When I talk to Young,
he never refuses me.
He always talks to me
and follows what I'm saying.
He never lets the words fall
down or makes atmosphere cold.
Because I talked to Young today,
talk about his work experence,
and some things we used to do.
I think people honestly
facing their own desires
and true demands,
It’s a very very difficult thing.
Go, time to eat.
Let's go.
Joel.
Coming.
Time to eat.
What are we eating today?
Today we have bread.
Bread and fried dough sticks.
We two will just have coffee.
Two don't drink milk.
Yes, he doesn't drink milk.
Then I'll do this.
Wishing for a bowl of soy milk.
Your wish didn't come true.
You only have Young.
No "wish."
Wow.
So witty.
Why so early?
I'll go.
Everyone is focusing on
what's in front of them.
Me too.
I'm focused on peeling my egg.
Here it comes.
We're going to a new place today.
Because it says.
XY Beach Map is now open.
Everyone please get ready
to start today's
beach trip.
Just so happens there's sun today.
Does it say there's a task?
No.
Of course there must be tasks on the beach.
I think there is.
Run and jump.
Then let's eat quickly.
After eating, hurry and get ready.
Already can't wait
to go to the beach.
A breezy summer outfit.
Changing clothes?
Then we're off.
Let's go, change clothes.
What are you wearing, Tyler?
Wearing a little shirt.
Is it carefully styled?
So impressive.
It'll be very sunny today.
Let's hydrate more before going out.
It's hot today, right?
Let me spray for you.
Oops.
Let me spray your feet.
Is that okay?
You didn't get the back just now.
The back too.
Sprayed it all on my hand.
OK.
I'll get the back of your calf
here.
OK.
Thanks.
Then let's set off.
I already see a card.
Let's see what it is.
Open it and read it out loud.
PROJECT XY,
will soon welcome the seventh member.
He will have a special privilege.
Get ready
to welcome the new member.
No.
Let's quickly find him and see.
So where is he?
But there's one here.
Can't see it.
It's earphones.
He has earphones.
It should be his token.
Then you two should have a lot in common.
So he should like listening to music.
He's like you.
This is his earphone case.
Yes, he loves music.
(Next Episode)
So which way will he come from?
He'll appear from behind us later.
No, actually it's a drop-in.
There's a helicopter.
And then he comes down.
Is the newbie here?
Over there.
"Project XY"